Sreelatha Vallabhaneni

Full-Stack Web Developer and Software Tester

I am an energetic and imaginative young web and Mobile app developer, passionate about creating user friendly and responsive websites while being motivated to learn new technologies in a fast pace, proven experience and success working as software test engineer as an individual and team member. comprehensive talents across the design development, testing, debugging and documentation of applications.



- sreelatha.vallabhaneni@gmail.com
- Høje-Taastrup, Denmark
- in linkedin.com/in/sreelatha-vallabhaneni-37a406b9
- 71665956
- sreelatha-portfolio.netlify.app/
- github.com/Sreelatha-Vallabhaneni

EDUCATION

Full-Stack web developer HackYourFuture-Copenhagen

08/2019 - 05/2020

Copenhagen, Denmark

Masters in Signal Processing Blekinge Tekniska Högskola

2010 - 2013

Karlskrona, Sweden

FINAL PROJECT

Dashboard App (seasony.dk). (2020) 🗹

Developed a Dashboard App for visualizing sensor data from plants and a collaboration between HackYourFuture-CPH and seasony.dk, which is a startup specializing in vertical farming with robotics. It is Full-Stack application using ReactJS, Hooks, Storybook, Swagger for API documentation, NodeJS, KnexJS, MYSQL, ESLint, Prettier, Recharts, Firebase, Git, Github, Heroku etc..

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer winefamly

09/2020 - I dag

Copenhagen, Denmark

Software Tester Mavininfotech

2014 - 2014

Hyderabad, India

Software Tester

LiveTech

2013 - 2014

Hyderabad, India

Swedish

Limited Working Proficiency

Enalish

Professional Working Proficiency

Elementary Proficiency

HTML5

SKILLS

CSS3

Git

GitHub

Web package

JavaScript

NPM

ReactJS

Hooks

JIRA

Storybook

ExpressJS

Re charts **KnexJS**

D3.JS **REST API**

MYSQL

NodeJS

Workbench

Postman

Magento 2

Swagger

TypeScript

Less JS

Visual Studio

Expo

Firebase

Test Cases

Test Scenarios

Reactnative

Blackbox Testing

Re-testing

Regression Testing

HP OC

HP OTP

LINUX OS

SDLC

STLC

Functional Testing

CERTIFICATES

ISTQB Certificate

Prøve i Dansk 2 (PD2)

LANGUAGES

Telugu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Danish